Guide to the Andrew Wellington Cordier Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V:The United Nations Period And Related Files
  - Subseries V.2: Personal Correspondence and Administrative Files of Cordier
    - Sub-subseries V.2.6: Public Addresses & Papers, Honorary Degrees, Awards
      - 15 Nov 1955 University of Denver, Social Science Foundation (recorded interview at UN) (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 18 Nov 1955 United States Industrial College of the Armed Forces, UN Hq. (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 24 Nov 1955 National Council for the Social Studies,(UN Rq). First General Session, Mr. Cordier, Chairman (speakers Hammarskjold, Bunche, Munro, Bokhari) (Text on file: Yes) (Box 64)
      - 29 Nov 1955 US Army War College, UN Hq. (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 6 Dec 1955 The Indiana Council of Churches, UN Seminar. Dinner meeting, Beekman Tower Hotel, New York NY (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 17 & 18 1956 Jan Lectures, Special Interne Program, United Nations NY 1956 1. Origins and the Drafting of the Charter (Box 64)
      - 2. General Assembly (Summaries by Interns) (Box 64)
      - 20 Jan 1956 CARE (Co-operative for American Remittances to Everywhere). Visiting Field Workers, briefing. UN Hq. (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 3 Feb 1956 Presbyterian Church, UN Seminar, UN Hq. (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 3 Feb 1956 Church of the Brethren group, UN Hq. (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 15 Feb 1956 Non-Governmental Organizations, weekly briefing UN Hq. "Impact of Decisions made at the Tenth Session of the General Assembly upon the Future of the Organization. (Text on file: Yes, unedited transcript) (Box 64)
      - 2 Mar 1956 Indiana University, Bloomington, Indiana. Little United Nations Assembly, University Convocation. "United Nations Begins its Second Decade" (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 3 Mar 1956 Church of the Brethren, Trotwood Church, Trotwood, Ohio (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 7 Mar 1956 U.S. Military Academy, Vest Point, N.Y. (Meeting sponsored by West Point Women's Club) (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 10 Mar 1956 International House, New York. Conference on the United Nations, closing address. (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 11 Mar 1956 Manhasset Congregational Church, young 1 adult group (Manhasset, NY) (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 17 Mar 1956 Columbia Scholastic Press Association, luncheon meeting, Waldorf Astoria (32nd Annual Convention). "Behind the Scenes at the United Nations" (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 19 Mar 1956 Columbia Broadcasting System "See it Now" (file Folder but no contents?) (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 22 Mar 1956 Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development (National Education Association 1), UN Hq. "Beginning the Second Decade of the United Nations" (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 29 Mar 1956 Dayton Council on World Affairs, student group, UN Hq.--briefing (Box 64)
      - 19 Apr 1956 World Affairs Council of Philadelphia; Seventh Annual Model UN General Assembly, Univ. of Penn. Museum, Philadelphia. "UN Begins its 2nd Decade" (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 22 Apr 1956 Neshaminy School District, Langhorne, Penna., dedication of Junior-Senior High School "The Place of Education in World Affairs" (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 3 Jun 1956 MaCMurray College, commencement address? "On Being an Answer to Life's Problems" (Text on file: Yes) (Box 64)
      - 5 Jun 1956 Ball State Teachers College, Muncie, Indiana, commencement address. "Education in the Atomic Age" (Text on file: Yes) (Box 64)
      - 16 Jun 1956 Haverford College, Haverford, Pa. Alumni Association Centenary Forum. "Educating for International Understanding." (Text on file: Yes) (Box 64)
      - 16 Jun 1956 WCAU, Philadelphia Television Panel "Scope" (see Haverford College file above) (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 24 Sep 1956 General Board of World Peace, Methodist Church,UN Hq. (annual meeting, New York) (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 25 Sep 1956 Naval War College, Newport., Rhode Island. "International Organizations" (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 3 Oct 1956 Great Neck Public Schools, Creat Neck, N.Y Adult Program Seminar "The World and Peace" (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 19 Oct 1956 University of Pittsburgh. YMCA-YWCA group visit to New York and UN. Briefing at UN Hq (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 21 Oct 1956 Protestant Council of the City of New York: United Nations Convocation, Riverside Church (in cooperation with the American Association for the UN) "The United Nations as an Effective Instrument for Peace (Text on file: Yes) (Box 64)
      - 24 Oct 1956 United Nations Association of Maryland, UN Day TV Program--recorded by UN Radio-TV on 18 October (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 24 Oct 1946 Indiana State Commission on United Nations Day, Indianapolis. Interview by telephone in Mr. Cordier's office, UN, New York (questions &answers). Rebroadcast for UN Day Program (Text on file: No, except for questions) (Box 64)
      - 4 Nov 1956 First Methodist Church, Bluffton, Indiana. Long distance telephone address from UN, New York (Text on file: No) (Box 64)
      - 16 Nov 1956 United Nations Radio program. "On the Record"; interview with Mr. Cordier by Irving Berenson of UN Radio (broadcast over CBS and Canadian Broadcasting). Topic "United Nations Emergency Force in the Middle East (Text on file: No, except for questions) (Box 64)
      - 4 Jan 1957 Press Conference, UN Headquarters. Subject: Middle East: UN Emergency Force and Suez Settlement (Interview followed Mr. Cordier's trip to Cairo and Beirut Dec-Jan) (Text on file: Yes) (Box 65)
      - 8 Jan 1957 Heifer Project Inc. Board of Directors, dinner at Paris house, Park Avenue Christian Church" New York City (Box 65)
      - 14 Jan 1957 International Press Institute, 2nd United Nations Seminar, Carnegie Building, New York (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 18 Jan 1957 The National War College of Washington, D.C. Visit to UN Hq. Subject: Mr. Cordier's recent trip to Egypt, clearance of the Suez Canal, etc. (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 8 Feb 1957 Church of the Brethren, Brooklyn, N.Y., Youth Group, visit to UN Hq. (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 8 Mar 1957 Church of the Brethren, Brooklyn, N.Y., Adult Group, visit to UN Hq. (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 21 Mar 1957 National meeting, UN Hq. East." Editorial Association, annual spring Commodore Hotel, New York. Visit to "The United Nations and the Middle East." (Text on file: Yes) (Box 65)
      - 25 Apr 1957 American Association for the United Nations, closed circuit TV program (CBS) from UN Hq. 'Conference room 4. Discussion panel, Cordier, Bunche, Gross, Wadsworth, Hoffman, M"B. Roosevelt, AWC topic --"Suez' Canal" Bunche topic --"UNEF" (Text on file: Yes, Bunche and Cordier) (Box 65)
      - 30 Apr 1957 North Shore Chapter, American Association for the United Nations, Manhasset, N.Y. "Problems of Creating a UN Emergency Force" (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 17 May 1957 The University of Michigan Club of New York luncheon, UN Hq. "Highlights on the UN" (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 19 May 1957 Purdue University, Lafayette, Indiana. International Federation of Agricultural Producers, 10th anniversary celebration. Statement by Mr. Cordier conveying message from Mr. Hammarskjold, Secretary-General UN (Text on file: Yes) (Box 65)
      - 28 May 1957 New York Alumni Chapter of Alpha Kappa Psi Fraternity, Annual Founders' Day Dinner, Midston House, New York. "Suez and Near East" (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 4 Jun 1957 Naval War College, Newport, R.I. Global Strategy Discussions. AWC topic: "Factors Producing the Current World Situation" (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 10 Jun 1957 Indiana University, Bloomington, Indiana. Honorary degree and Commencement Address (citation text on file but no, speech text) (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 14 Jul 1957 American Bar Association, meeting at UN Hq., General Assembly Hall. Opening remarks by Mr. Cordier. Other speakers, Stavropoulos and Sir ,Leslie Munro and Ambassador Wadsworth (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 30 Jul 1957 University of Pennsylvania Summer School, course on the US and World Affairs. Philadelphia, Pa. "The United Nations" (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 19 Aug 1957 United Nations Interne group, UN Hq. "Political Role of the Secretary-General" (Text on file: Yes, resume, unedited) (Box 65)
      - 26 Aug 1957 Indiana District of Kiwanis International, 40th annual convention, French Lick, Indiana "The United Nations" (Text on file: Yes—"notes" done by Mr. Cordier) (Box 65)
      - 27 Aug 1957 Rotary Club, Kokomo, Indiana., "United Nations" (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 6 Sep 1957 Recorded interview, City of New York, Municipal Broadcasting System WNYC. "International Interview" program. ",(focus on 12th session General Assembly(recorded at UN Hq.) (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 8 Oct 1957 Greater Worcester Area Council of Churches, Worcester, Mass. Visit to New York 1-10 October (UN Seminar.) "United Nations" (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 17 Oct 1957 The National War College, Washington --group visit to United Nations. "Role of the Secretary-General" (Box 65)
      - 24 Oct 1951 World Affairs Council' of Philadelphia, luncheon commemorating 275th landing of William Penn and 12th anniversary of the United Nations, Warwick Hotel, Philadelphia "William Penn and the UN" (2 Folders, one for correspondence, one for text) (Text on file: Yes) (Box 65)
      - 24 Oct 1957 Philadelphia's Junior Town Meeting of the Air, NBC-WRCV, Philadelphia. Tape recorded in William Penn Charter School, Germantown. Topic of broadcast "Is the United Nations Contributing to the Abolition of War?" (Text on file: Yes, but not full text) (Box 65)
      - 18 Nov 1957 La Hermosa Project (Inter American Community Center), dinner, Riverside Church, New York City. (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 23 Nov 1957 Christian Citizenship Conference, Ohio Area of the Methodist Church, Columbus, Ohio. "Christian Citizenship and World Peace" (Text on file: Yes) (Box 65)
      - 2 Dec 1957 Indiana Council of Churches, UN Seminar 1-6 Dec, New York.. Briefing at UN Hq. (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 2 Dec 1957 Parliamentary Dinner honoring Lester B. Pearson (Nobel Peace Prize 1957), Ottawa, Canada. (Text on file: Yes) (Box 65)
      - ? Dec 1957 Dartmouth College group at UN Hq. "Role of the Secretary-General" (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 1 January 1958 250th Anniversary of the founding of Church of the Brethren, Inaugural program, Germantown, Pennsylvania (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 12 Jan 1958 New York Times Youth Forums, Telecast on channel 5, 12 Jan; (Broadcast WQXR 18 January).Moderator, Dorothy Gordon. Guest: Mr. Cordier. Topic: "Does the World Lack Leadership to Maintain Peace.'" (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 14 Jan 1958 Disciples of Christ, UN Seminar (arranged by United Christian Missionary Society). Visit to UN Hq. (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 22 Jan 1958 Nieman Fellows, visit to UN Hq. "United Nations as a Diplomatic Instrument". (Box 65)
      - 30 Jan 1958 UN Secretariat Discussion Group, UN Hq. "Changing Role of the General Assembly" (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 7 Feb 1958 Great Neck High School, adult and student group (5 foreign student guests American Field Service). Evening meeting (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 7 Feb 1958 Bell Telephone Executives at UN Hq. (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 14 Feb 1958 National Farmers Union group at UN Hq., 1958 trainee program (Text on file: No) (Box 65)
      - 19 Feb 1958 International Business Machines Corp., group of executives, visit to UN Hq. (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 22 Feb 1958 American Friends Service Committee, annual California High School Civil Liberties Conference, Asilomar, Cal. "American Leadership and World Freedom". Panel program, foreign students (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 23 Feb 1958 University of Chicago Club, San Francisco and San Francisco Chapter American Association of the United Nations, reception for Mr Cordier Sunday, 23 February "United Nations", speech & questions. (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 24 Feb 1958 University of Utah, Salt Lake City. 10th annual Pi Sigmr. Alpha Lecture, Spencer Hall auditorium. "Evaluation of the role of the United Nations in World Affairs" (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 25 Feb 1958 Washburn University of Topeka. "The United) Nations, the United States & World Peace" (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 13 Mar 1958 Friends General Conference, Carnegie Building, New York. City. Conference theme: "Issues Before the United Nations Today" (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 20 Mar 1958 Association of Social Studies Chairmen, New York City, World Affairs Center for the US, UN Plaza, New York. "An Evaluation of the Role of the United Nations in World Affairs" (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 26 Mar 1958 American Society for Public Administration,1958 National Conference, International Section, visit to UN Hq. (Box 66)
      - 1 May 1958 United States Committee for United Nations Children's Fund (UNICEF) Annual Meeting, morning session. "Role of Citizen Organizations, etc. (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 21 May 1958 American Association for the United Nations, Great Neck Chapter, evening meeting, Great Neck Junior High School. "A UN oriented foreign policy for the United States" (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 3 Jun 1958 General Federation of Women's Clubs, Convention, Detroit, Mich. "The United Nations in an Unsettled World" (Text on file: Yes, resume) (Box 66)
      - 18 Oct 1958 Oberlin College, .Oberlin, Ohio. Anniversary Convocation (125th). Honorary degree. (no speech ?) (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 1 Nov 1958 Indiana Central College, Indianapolis, Indiana, dedication service, new Academic Hall. "Making Education Effective in Today's World" (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 2 Nov 1958 Manchester Church of the Brethren, Sunday worship (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 7 Nov 1958 Public Relations Society of America Annual Conference, New York City. Briefing, UN Hq. (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 11 Nov 1958 Disciples of Christ, UN Seminar group (arranged by 'United Christian Missionary Society). Visit to UN Hq (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 17 Nov 1958 American Committee to Benefit Arab Refugees, benefit dinner, Waldorf Astoria Hotel, New York. (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 20 Nov 1958 University of Chicago Alumni Association, panel discussion at United Nations. Cordier, chairman: speakers, John McDiarmid, Ralph Bunche, Dag Hammarskjold. (File 1, correspondence; File #2 text). (Text on file: Yes, partially edited draft) (Box 66)
      - 22 Nov 1958 American Association for the United Nations, Biennial Convention, dinner meeting, Roosevelt Hotel, New York City (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 10 Dec 1958 UNESCO exhibit commemorating 10th anniversary of Universal Declaration of Human Rights, opening. Presentation of plaque by Mr. Cordier to award winner. ? (suggested draft) (Box 66)
      - 18 Dec 1958 Council on Foreign Relations, discussion group on the United Nations. (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 7 Jan 1959 Ohio Wesleyan University, Delaware, Ohio. (Chapel Assembly series) (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 13 Jan 1959 Board of World Peace, Methodist Church, UN Seminar for the Illinois Area, New York City. (UN Hq.) "Review and Evaluation of the 13th General Assembly UN" (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 22 Jan 1959 League of Women Voters, taped interview, UN Hq. "Role of the Secretary-General" (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 21 Jan 1959 The Rockefeller Institute, student dinner. "United Nations" (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 24 Jan 1959 (1) Indiana Broadcasters visit to UN Hq. ,(Group from Indianapolis and Fort Wayne, Ind. (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 24 Jan 1959(2) Taped interview with Bud Stone, Station WOWO, Fort Wayne, Indiana (done at UN Hq.) (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 9 Feb 1959 The Oberlin Club of New York, annual banquet of tie Oberlin Alumni, Waldorf Astoria, New York City. "One World or None --A Challenge to the College Graduate" (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 7 Feb 1959 Non-Governmental Organization group, briefing, at UN Hq. "Behind the Scenes of the 13th General Assembly" (Resume) (Box 66)
      - 15 Feb 1959 Silvermine Guild 1959 Forum Series, New Canaan, Conn. "The Art of Living in a World Without Boundaries" (Box 66)
      - 17 Feb 1959 Pennsylvania State University, University Park, Pennsylvania, graduate lecture series. "The United Nations in a Revolutionary World" (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 6 Mar 1959 Church of the Brethren, Brooklyn. Visit to UN Hq. New York (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 9 Mar 1959 Peruvian Seminar of Indiana University, luncheon UN Hq. New York (arranged by International House) (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 23 Mar 1959 United Nations Information Centre Directors at UN Hq. New York. Topic "Role of the Secretary-General and the Question of Publicity in relation to that role." (Text on file: Yes) (Box 66)
      - 1 Apr 1959 The Associated Church Press annual meeting, New York City. "Quite Diplomacy" (UN Hq.) (Text on file: No) (Box 66)
      - 10 Apr 1959 Executives" Club of Chicago, luncheon meeting, Morrison Hotel, Chicago. "World Tensions and the United Nations role" (Text on file: Yes) See also spare copies Folder (Box 67)
      - 17 Apr 1959 George Williams College, Chicago. Jenkins Lecture. "Forces Contending for the Mind of Youth in the World Today" (Text on file: Yes) (Box 67)
      - 23 Apr 1959 Laymen's Movement for a Christian World, Wainwright House, Ryek N. Y. Topic --"The United Nations" (answers to questions) List of questions Mr. Cordier was asked to respond to (Box 67)
      - 24 Apr 1959 Johns Hopkins University and United Nations Association of Maryland, lecture course on the UN. "Can the United Nations Meet Today's Challenges?" (Text on file: No) (Box 67)
      - 3 May 1959 The New York Times Youth Forum, NBC, Rockefeller, Plaza, New York City. "Diplomatic Negotiations, How Much Should the Public Know?" (Text on file: No) (Box 67)
      - 5 May 1959 Manhattan Chapter, American Association for the United Nations, World Affairs Auditorium, NY City. "The United Nations in a World of Tension and Revolution" (Text on file: No) (Box 67)
      - 7 May 1959 National Citizens Committee for the World Health Organization; 2nd National Conference on World Health, Statler Hilton Hotel, Washington, D.C. "Experience of the UN In Maintaining World Peace and... building for peace." (Text on file: No) (Box 67)
      - 19 May 1959 American Foundation for Overseas Blind (The Helen Keller World Crusade for the Blind), mtg. honoring Helen Keller, UN Hq., New York. "Conserving Human Resources, a World Goal"(Text on file: Yes) (Box 67)
      - 20 May 1959 The Speakers' Research Committee for the United Nations, Delegates Dining Room, UN Hq. New York. (Text on file: No) (Box 67)
      - 1 Jun 1951 Manchester College, North Manchester, Indiana. Commencement address. "Making Life Effective in a Troubled World." (Text on file: No) (Box 67)
      - 3 or 4 Jun 1959 Deckerville Community Schools (Deckerville, Michigan): group visit to UN Hq., New York (Text on file: No) (Box 67)
      - 10 Jun 1959 New York University, New York," N Y. Honorary Degree, Doctor of Laws. (no address) (text of citation) (Box 67)
      - 13 Jun 1959 University of Chicago Alumni Association, Alumni Day luncheon. Mr. Cordier recipient of Alumni Medal. "The United Nations in a World of Tension and Revolution" (Text on file: Yes) (Box 67)
      - 19 Jun 1959 Annual Conference, Church of the Brethren, Ocean Grove, N.J. (250th Anniversary) "Spiritual Resources in an Anxious World" (Text on file: No) (Box 67)
      - 3 Ju1 1959 Michigan State University, East Lansing, Mich. (College of Education and Summer Institute of Asia). Summer Lecture Series. "United Nations in a World of Tension and Revolution." (Text on file: No) (Box 67)
      - 28 Jun 1959 East Nimishillen Church of t he Brethren, North Canton, Ohio. Sunday worship. Pamphlet with comments by Mr. Cordier on a poem by Emma Lazarus appearing on the Statue of Liberty (Box 67)
      - Aug 1959 Preface by AWC to "A Chronology of the United Nations 1951-1958" by Chamberlin, et al, Oceana Publications. (Text on file: Yes) (Box 67)
      - 24 Oct 1959 Martha Kinney Cooper Ohioana .Library Assoc., annual meeting and authors' luncheon, Neil Rouse, Columbus, Ohio. (Mr. Cordier recipient of Ohioana Career medal for 1959) 1. Text of citation, 2. Text of address (Box 67)
      - 24 Oct 1959 Columbus Area UN Week Committee, UN Day commemoration, Columbus Ohio (Ohio State House grounds) (Text on file: No) (Box 67)
      - 25 Oct 1959 Zion Evangelical and Reformed Church, North Canton, Ohio. Sunday Worship. (Text on file: No) (Box 67)
      - 6 Nov 1959 State Teachers College of Indiana, Pennsylvania. visit of Shakespearean Club to New York. Visit to UN Uq.) (Text on file: No) (Box 67)
      - 20 Dec 1959 National Council of Churches, Pilgrimage program, ABC Radio. (Taped on 16 Dec 1959) (Text on file: No) (Box 67)
      - 7 Jan 1960 Women's International League for Peace and Freedom "Peace Initiative Series". Recorded Interview; "The World Community"(at UN Hq.? New York) (Text on file: No) (Box 68)
      - 15 Jan 1960 Non-Governmental Organizations Representatives at UN Hq. "14th Session of the UN General Assembly" --briefing and questions (Text on file: Yes) (Box 68)
      - 18 Jan 1960 United Christian Missionary Society, of Indianapolis, Indiana. Visit to UN Hq. New York (Disciples of Christ UN Seminar) (Text on file: No) (Box 68)
      - 5 Jan 1960 Brethren Youth Seminar, UN Hq. New York (Text on file: No) (Box 68)
      - 12 Feb 1960 Zionist Organization of America, UN Seminar, UN Hq., New York (Text on file: No) (Box 68)
      - 18 Feb 1960 US Department of State Foreign Service Inst. Class, UN Hq., New York., "United States Diplomacy and the, United Nations" (Text on file: No) (Box 68)
      - 26 Feb 1960 American Friends Service Committee, meeting of Representative Council, UN Hq., New York. "Recent sessions of the General Assembly and development work of the UN (Text on file: No) (Box 68)
      - 28 Feb 1960 Church of the Brethren, Trotwood, morning Worship, sermon (Text on file: No) (Box 68)
      - No file --28 Feb 1960 Telecast, Dayton Ohio Council on World Affairs, Dayton (see reference in Church of Brethren file) (Text on file: No) (Box 68)
      - 28 Feb 1960 Church Federation of Greater Dayton Convocation on International Affairs, National Cash Register Auditorium, Dayton, Ohio. "Our Interdependent World, Peril or Promise" (Text on file: No) (Box 68)
      - 4 Mar 1960 Church of the Brethren group (Brooklyn), UN Hq., New York (Text on file: No) (Box 68)
      - 8 Mar 1960 Hanover College Institute, Hanover, Indiana. Yes "Christian Values in International Diplomacy" (Text on file: Yes) (Box 68)
      - 18 Mar 1960 Second Peruvian Law Seminar of Indiana Univ. visit to UN Hq. (arrangements by International House, New York). (Text on file: No) (Box 68)
      - 18 Mar 1960 Catholic Editors, UN Hq., New York (Text on file: No) (Box 68)
      - 20 Mar 1960 Rotary and Kiwanis, North Manchester, Ind. (Text on file: No) (Box 68)
      - 21 Mar 1960 Manchester College, North Manchester, .Ind. Chapel address. (Text on file: No) (Box 68)
      - 21 Mar 1960 Rotary Club, Fort Wayne, Indiana. International Night. (Foreign Students from Indiana Technical Co1ege). (Text on file: No) (Box 68)
      - 21 Mar 1960 Associated Churches of Fort Wayne, Fort Wayne, Indiana (Text on file: No) (Box 68)